lionairthai.com 2018-01-13

# Privacy Policy

* * *

**Thai Lion Air Privacy Policy** Thai Lion Air is concerned about your right to privacy. Therefore, Thai Lion Air pledges to be responsible when gathering your personal information and to protect your privacy in every possible way. Although, this Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights, however, it does serve as an expression of Thai Lion Air’s commitment to protecting private personal information.

It must be borne in mind that Thai Lion Air reserves the right to change, amend and/or vary this Privacy Policy at any time and will notify users of the same by updating the policy here and by including a "NEWLY UPDATED" label with the "PRIVACY POLICY" link on the web sites governed by this policy for a period of 30 days.

This Privacy notice aims to answer your questions about the sources and kinds of information Thai Lion Air collects, how it is used, when it may be shared with others, and how we safeguard its confidentiality and security. We also provide you with ways to correct the data you provide us and the option to limit our sharing of this data with Thai Lion Air’s authorized third parties.   
**Information collection** To ensure that we successfully process your booking and to effectively manage our business, we collect and maintain personal information about you. We collect customer information from many sources for the purposes of understanding current or new demands, meeting these demands as well as to provide and personalize our services. The means of information collection, among others, are as following: 

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback.

  * From you; when you voluntarily provide to us or to third party service provider(s) engaged by us;
  * From your browser; when you visit our website and your browser interacts with us;
  * From other sources and related links in connection with providing your transportation and/or accommodation needs and services;
  * From you; when you voluntarily provide to us or to third party service provider(s) engaged by us;
  * From your browser; when you visit our website and your browser interacts with us;
  * From other sources and related links in connection with providing your transportation and/or accommodation needs and services;
  * The personal information we collect about you may include but not limited to the following:
  * Name, addresses and telephone numbers
  * Email addresses, fax numbers and mobile numbers
  * Flight information or details
  * Credit / Charge card number(s), including associated billing address(es) and expiration date(s)
  * Information necessary to facilitate travel or other services, including travel companion(s) names, emergency contacts, seating preferences and special dietary or medical needs
  * Passport number, nationality and country of residence
  * Use of products and services such as self-service devices, flight status notification and online check-in
  * Personal information provided via survey, contest, competition or other marketing research efforts
  * Personal information provided to customer-service representatives to research and resolve issues or questions or lodging complain
  * Corporate-contract, employer and/or other corporate affiliation (i.e. employer name, title, address and contact information)
  * We also collect your information when you make or send job application via our official website @ www.Thai Lion Air.com.

**Use of information collection** Generally, we use your information for administrative purpose e.g. processing, confirming, fulfilling and completing your transactions and requests for our services. In the event there is alteration / change of flight schedule, we will use information provided by you while making your reservation through our official website @ www.LionAirThai.com, our call center, our sales counter, to contact and notify you of the alteration / change. In addition to this, your information will be used for the purposes of accounting (billing and auditing), immigration, custom control, safety, security, statistical and marketing analysis, information systems management, system testing, maintenance and development, operational, support, customer surveys, customer relations and to improve and help us in any future dealings with you, for example by identifying your requirements and preferences.

In employment scenario, we would use information that you voluntarily provide to compare against the job specification / criteria we are seeking / intending to employ. 

Whenever required by law, we will disclose your information to the government bodies or authorities or third parties pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process accordingly. Further, we may also use or disclose your information as permitted by law to protect the rights or property of Thai Lion Air, our customers, our website, or its users. We may also disclose your information, whether in part or in full, to our contracted or authorized companies such as our data processors.

As part of our effort to serve you better, we are constantly enhancing and expanding our services to fulfill your ever-growing needs. In order to realize this business aim, we will from time to time appoint, authorize or contract with strategic business partner. Your information will be disclosed to these business partners, authorized or contracted third party, service providers or advertisers to make available promotions, offers, products or services, which may not belong to us. However, to ensure that you will not receive unwanted communications, only information with regards to promotions, offers, products or services that you selected or marked as interested through our member profile will be shared with the respective business partners, service providers or third parties. 

In the circumstances set out in this policy where Thai Lion Air passes your information to a third party, we will ensure that the security measures that such party has in place in relation to the processing of your data are at least as stringent as those employed by Thai Lion Air if not better. This does not apply where we are required by law to pass your information to a third party. In the event we go through a business transition, such as sale of part or all of our assets, merger or acquisition, your information will likely form part of this transition and be transferred.

  * Sharing of information collected
  * Personal information we collect from you may be disclosed to:
  * Our bank for authorization of transaction and for payment
  * Relevant third parties eg. Booking agents and hotels
  * Authorized government bodies if legally required to do

Thai Lion Air does not sell or rent any personal information you provide on our web site to any other parties. Thai Lion Air may share anonymous and/or aggregated information about all our users with third parties. **Correction/updating personal information** The instructions to do this are clearly outlined in every piece of promotional material issued by Thai Lion Air. 

Links to other sites Thai Lion Air web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you. Thai Lion Air's privacy policy applies solely to information collected by Thai Lion Air on this web site.

 **Security** Our online reservation system resides on a secure server that encrypts your purchase information using Secure Socket Layers. We use all reasonable endeavors to protect personal information from loss, misuse and alteration. Only authorized employees and agents, who are under appropriate confidentiality obligations, will have access to your personal information. However, you will be responsible for any user ID or password that is used on our web site. You should take due care to protect them.

 **Cookies** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.

This enables our system to recognize your browser and remember your passenger names and billing information so that you won't have to retype it. The address and passenger information is saved to your hard drive by the Thai Lion Air web server. This information can only be accessed by the Thai Lion Air web server; Internet users and other companies cannot access this information. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

For security reasons, your credit card number is not saved. You must type the credit card number each time you make a purchase. 

We also utilize cookies to track the effectiveness of online advertising. This information is treated confidentially and will not be shared with anyone outside of Thai Lion Air. Thai Lion Air will only use this information to make informed decisions with regard to the purchase of online advertising. This enables Thai Lion Air to maintain low costs and low fares for you, our Customers. 

**Site tracking** We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the site to better meet the needs of visitors to Thai Lion Air.com. This software does not enable us to capture any personally identifying information. 

**Log files** We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
